dancemarathon.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy Policy | Children's Miracle Network Hospitals

##  What the Privacy Policy Covers/Does Not Cover

  * This policy covers how CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS treats personal information that CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS collects and receives from donors. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of local children's hospitals, companies that CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS does not own or control, or to people that CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK does not employ or manage.

##  Information Collecting and Use

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS collects personal information when you donate to CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS.

  * When you donate, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and zip code. Once you donate to CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK, you are not anonymous to us.

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and the page you request.

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS uses information for the following general purposes: to improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS will share your donor contact information with the CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS participating hospital selected during the donor's gift designation. The donor is advised to review the receiving institution's privacy policy to see how they will use their donor information.

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  *     * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

    * We transfer information about you if CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##  Correction/Updating Personal Information

You can change your donor information (name, address, etc…) in our database by contacting our customer support team at 801-278-8900, or by clicking here.

Donors who have previously opted-in to external communication lists and services, can also use the above contacts to inform CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS that you no longer wish to have your personal information shared outside of the organization.

##  Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

  * In certain areas CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions

##  Changes to This Privacy Policy

  * CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your CHILDREN'S MIRACLE NETWORK HOSPITALS account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please send them to us by clicking here.

Children's Miracle Network Hospitals  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
205 West 700 South  
Salt Lake City, UT 84101  
(801) 214.7400
